原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我叫卡拉·佐·艾尔
My name is Kara Zor-El.
我来自氪星
I'm from Krypton.
我来到这颗星球避难
I'm a refugee on this planet.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
我被派往地球保护我的堂弟
I was sent to Earth to protect my cousin.
但我的太空舱被击中后偏离路线
But my pod got knocked off course.
在我到达地球之时
And by the time I got here,
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我的堂弟已经长大  成为了超人
my cousin had already grown up and become... Superman.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我隐藏了我的真实身份
I hid who I really was
直到最近的一起事故
until one day when an accident
迫使我向世界揭示了自己的身份
forced me to reveal myself to the world.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
对于大多数人  我只是凯特科全球媒体公司的记者
To most people, I'm a reporter at CatCo Worldwide Media.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
但私下里  我与收养家庭的姐姐一同为超查部工作
But in secret I work with my adopted sister at the DEO
保护这颗我称之为家园的星球
to protect this planet I call my home
总监     你是不是饿得慌
不受任何人的伤害
from anyone that means to cause it harm.
我是超女
I am Supergirl.
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
-我是尼娅  -尼娅  很高兴认识你
- I'm Nia. - Nia, it's so nice to meet you.
阿尔  菲奥纳在这吗
Al, is Fiona here?
不  她没来上班
No, she didn't show up for her shift.
你是谁
Who are you?
自由的代表
An agent of liberty.
奥蒂斯与默茜·格雷夫斯  姐弟小组
Otis and Mercy Graves, a brother and sister team.
我们是正义之士
We are the good guys.
为了拯救这个国家而战斗
Fighting to save this country.
你以为今晚你阻止了我们  但导火索已经引燃
You think you stopped us tonight, but the fuse was lit.
-你抓住他们了吗  -只抓住一个
- Did you get them? - Only one.
戴维营刺杀未遂事件揭示了
The assassination attempt has revealed
总统是一个外星人
that the President is an alien.
没有仇恨  没有恐惧
世界和平
Peace for all!
叛徒  停止入侵
蟑螂快滚出来
Roaches out, now!
外星人滚回老家
地球欢迎所有人
-总统女士  -超女
- Madam President? - Supergirl.
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
您真的有必要辞职吗
Are you sure resigning is necessary?
肯定还有其他办法
There must be another way.
我任职总统一事触犯了《宪法》第二条
My presidency is in violation of Article 2 of the Constitution.
如果我留下来经历弹劾
If I stay and fight impeachment,
只会引起更多的混乱和骚动
it will only cause more chaos and turmoil.
您做了那么多好事
You've done so much good.
人们应该记住这一点
People need to remember that.
您担任总统期间一直在唤起大家的同情心
Every step of your presidency promoted compassion,
提倡人人享有平等权利
and equal rights for all...
说实话  在某种程度上  这对我是一种解脱
To be honest, there is a part of me that is relieved.
隐藏自己的身份很辛苦
Hiding who I am, it's taken its toll.
我能理解
I can understand that.
默茜·格雷夫斯暴露您的身份
Mercy Graves exposed you
是因为她想煽动人们心中的恐惧和愤怒
because she wanted to fan the flames of fear and hatred.
我会阻止她的  我向您保证
And I will stop her. I promise you that.
一旦她暴露之后
And once she's exposed,
人们会发现根本不需要对您怀有恐惧
people will realize they never had to fear you.
恐惧能创造出原本不存在的怪物
Fear can create monsters where none existed before.
你要提醒人们这世界上仍然存有善良
Remind the world that there is still goodness here.
做那盏我们需要的希望灯塔
Be that beacon of hope that we still need.
我不会让您失望的  总统女士
I won't let you down, Madam President.
叛徒  叛徒  叛徒
Traitor! Traitor! Traitor!
滚回你的星球去
Go back to your planet,
我们这里不需要你  邪恶的蟑螂
we don't need you here, you ugly roach!
恶人做恶事  所以邪恶的是你才对
Ugly is as ugly does. That makes you the ugly one.
我们要世界和平  人人平等
Peace and equality for all.
现在我们应该平心静气地谈谈
Now is the time to talk to each other,
而不是打架
not fight.
超 女
第四季 第二集
我辞职之后
As I step down,
将由副总统贝克担任总司令
I put my full confidence in Vice President Baker
我对他充满信心
as Commander-in-Chief.
她是个叛徒  应该被关进超查部的监狱
She's a traitor, she belongs in one of our cages.
隐藏身份并不代表她就是罪犯
Not revealing her identity doesn't make her a criminal.
她就是罪犯
Yeah, it does.
她强行控制了我们的民主  不值得被信任
She's hijacked our democracy. She can't be trusted.
别打了
Knock it off!
这里是工作场所
This is a workplace.
想谈论政治的话  别占用上班的时间
If you want to discuss politics then do it on your own time.
我们的任务是保护所有公民
Our mission here is to defend all citizens,
无论是人类还是外星人
that is human and alien alike.
回你们各自的岗位上去吧
Now, get back to your stations.
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers,
我按照你的要求把奥蒂斯·格雷夫斯带到了审讯室
I moved Otis Graves into interrogation like you asked.
谢谢你  詹森  我这就过去
Thanks, Jensen, I'll be right down.
总统怎么样了
How is the president doing?
我看到她没有接受特赦
I saw she didn't take the pardon.
她不想引起进一步的混乱
She didn't want to cause any more chaos.
默茜的弟弟开口了吗
Has Mercy's brother talked?
关于她的下落有线索了吗
Do we have a lead on her location?
奥蒂斯跟我装傻  但他在保护她
Otis plays dumb, but he's protecting her.
他只告诉我  暴露总统的身份只是第一阶段
All he's given me is that the president was just phase one.
我们不会让事情发展到第二阶段
Well, we won't let it get to phase two.
美国人民仍然心存同情
This country still has compassion and empathy.
我可以劝服他们
I can still reach them.
昨天我或许还会相信你
Yesterday I would have believed you
但现在恐怕发生了根本性的变化
but now I fear that something fundamental has shifted.
你为什么遇事总是这么悲观呢
Why do you always insist on making our collective glass half empty?
我刚刚给本部的同事劝完架
I just broke up a fight between our own people here in the DEO.
我给你看样东西
And let me show you something.
布莱尼搜索了在暗网上找到的
Brainy ran a search on all the anti-alien threads
所有反外星人跟帖
that you found on the dark web.
这是昨晚的跟帖数
That was last night
当时大家还不知道总统是杜兰星人
before the world found out the president was a Durlan.
而这是今早的跟帖数
This was from this morning.
L公司工作证
等一下
Hold it.
抱歉刚才失礼了
Sorry I was rude.
我有急事
I'm just in a bit of a rush.
我不会往心里去的
Oh, I don't take things personal.
你知道新闻里是怎么评论我们的吗
Do you know what they're saying about us on the news?
他们说我们是地球的寄生虫
They're saying we're infesting this planet.
他们往道德低点走  我们往道德高点走
You know, they go low, we go high.
我们会挺过去的
We'll get through this.
阿尔
Hey, Al,
菲奥纳今天来上班了吗
Fiona make it in today?
没有  她已经三次轮班没来了
No, she's missed three shifts.
这不像她的风格
It's not like her.
有人联系过她未婚夫吗
Anyone speak to her fiance?
他在英国
He's in England.
你知道她住在哪里吗
You wouldn't happen to know where she lives, would you?
稍等
Give me a sec.
莎拉  你来做都市新闻
Sarah, I've got you on metro,
看看你能从市长办公室打听到什么消息
see what you can get from the mayor's office.
我正在写一个专题
Uh, I'm doing a feature
关于默茜·格雷夫斯源于L公司的犯罪史
on Mercy Graves's criminal history starting at Luthor Corp.
只写事实  不要借题发挥
Only facts, no spin.
明白  不掺杂个人感情
Got it. Clean and steady, check.
各位  还有新闻等着我们去报道呢
All right, guys, the news is not going to report itself
开工吧
let's get to work.
奥尔森先生  你现在有空吗
Mr. Olsen, do you have a minute?
当然  尼娅  什么事
Of course, Nia, what's up?
我想知道  作为主编
I was just wondering if as the Editor-in-Chief,
你是否会就总统的外星人身份
you were going to write an editorial
写一篇社论
on where the paper stands on this issue.
阐明本报的立场
Of the president being an alien.
现在我们需要关注事实
Um, right now, we need to focus on facts.
这才是重点
That's what we need.
好的
Okay.
-我这就去做  -谢谢
- I'm on it. - Thank you.
我再问你一次
All right, let's try this again.
默茜杀了一大批特勤局特工之后
Where does Mercy usually like to go after she's killed
通常会去什么地方
a few dozen secret service agents?
第六大街的意大利餐厅
That Italian place on 6th Street.
我没在跟你开玩笑
This isn't a joke.
那家餐厅的长棍面包好吃极了
Neither are their bread sticks.
我懂了
Okay, I get it.
在外面  一切由你姐姐做主  对吧
Out there, it's your sister that's the boss, right?
但在这里  我才是老大
But in here, I'm the boss,
我可以让你痛不欲生
and I can make your life extremely miserable.
我知道
Oh, I know.
我听说过超查部的故事
I have heard stories about the DEO.
你们向大气中散播铅粉
Poisoned a boatload of Daxamites
毒害了一批达克萨姆人
by lacing the atmosphere with lead?
砰
Kablooey!
你们真是心狠手辣
You're cruel as ice.
我猜你们还把那台铅粉散播器留作战利品了吧
I bet you even keep that lead dispersal device around as a trophy.
知道吗
You know what?
默茜很聪明  不会把逃跑计划告诉你
Mercy's too smart to tell a plan like that to you.
你为何这么恶毒呢
Why do you got to be so mean?
詹森  把这个聪明鬼押回他的牢房去
Jensen, take Einstein here back up to his containment cell.
继续找吧  老大
Keep searching, boss.
那两个人现在已经躲得远远的了
Those two are so far underground by now,
说不定在中国呢
they're probably in China.
奥蒂斯说漏嘴了
Otis slipped up.
他提到默茜时  说的是"那两个人"
When he was talking about Mercy, he referred to "Those two."
所以她在和别人合作  我们得找出是谁
So she's working with another person, we got to figure who it is.
也许是她在卢瑟公司认识的人
Maybe it's someone she knew at Luthor Corp.
我现在去找莉娜  我会查出来的
I'm heading to Lena's now. I'll try to find out.
今天白宫外的抗议者发生了暴乱
A riot broke out today among protesters at the White House.
幸运的是  超女也在场...
Luckily, Supergirl was there to...
那些觉得从婴儿手上拿走糖果很简单的人
People who think taking candy from a baby is easy,
肯定没有试过从青春期宅男手上抢电脑
have never taken a laptop from a prepubescent computer nerd.
看这超女到处行善
Look at Supergirl peddling help.
她会成为我们的麻烦  对吧
She's going to be a problem, isn't she?
是的  但是我们可以控制住她
Yes. But one we can manage.
你从哪弄来的这个
Where did you get that?
网络上充斥着黑暗有趣的东西
The web is dark and full of fun things.
听着  这玩意你要谨慎使用
Listen to me, you have to be very careful about that.
我们不能让她成为烈士
We do not want to make her a martyr.
我们俩只会制造混乱而已
The only thing that you and I are going to create is chaos.
这个...
This...
只是个保护伞
...is just a security blanket.
敲敲门
Knock-knock.
卡拉
Kara!
我的天  见到你真好
Oh, my God. I am so glad to see you.
等一下  等一下
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
这是大肚腩汉堡吗
Is that Big Belly Burger?
我有说过你是我最喜欢的人吗
Have I ever told you you're my favorite person?
詹姆斯说你午饭和晚饭都在工作
James said you have been working through lunches and dinners.
没错
I have.
自从总统被揭露是外星人之后
Sales for the image inducers have been skyrocketing
形象诱发器的销量一飞冲天
ever since the revelation that the president is an alien.
你对这事怎么看
Yeah. How do you feel about that?
好像整个世界一夜之间都改变了
It's kind of like the whole world changed overnight.
说实话  我一开始就不怎么信任
To be honest, I didn't have very much faith
那些政客们
in politicians to begin with.
我觉得他们都不可信  谢谢
I don't think any of them can be trusted. Thank you.
我都不知道你这么愤世嫉俗
I had no idea you were so cynical.
你肯定知道
Of course you did.
说实话  我得称赞她下台的决定
To be honest though, I have to commend her for stepping down.
我们现在最不需要的
You know? The last thing we need right now
就是股市崩溃或是贸易禁令
is a tumbling stock market or trade embargoes
或是从这件事衍生出来的其他麻烦
or whatever other chaos can come out of this thing.
其实我们现在最不需要的
Well, actually the last thing we need
是让民主变为无政府状态
is democracy descending into anarchy.
你说得对  我们都不想要这种麻烦
You are right. Neither of us need that.
你最近怎么样
How are you doing?
挺艰难的  看着这么多人在斗争
It's hard. Seeing this many people fighting.
但詹姆斯正努力处理好凯特科的工作
But James is trying his best to manage it at CatCo.
站在双方的立场上做报道
You know, telling both sides of the story.
其实也是我来这里的第二个原因
Which is actually the second reason I'm here.
不知你能不能帮我完成一篇
I was wondering if you could help me with an article
关于默茜·格雷夫斯的文章
I'm writing about Mercy Graves.
默茜这人很复杂
Mercy's complicated.
不过她在卢瑟公司的工作都被记录下了
But, her work with Luthor Corp is well documented.
-我会把文件给你  -太好了
- I'll get you the files. - Great.
但是  要先吃汉堡
But, burgers first.
没错  汉堡永远优先
Yes, burgers always first.
访客
好了  听着  利用面部识别系统
All right, listen up. I want facial recognition
在所有地方寻找默茜·格雷夫斯
combing everywhere for Mercy Graves.
开始干活吧
Let's get to it.
你看来很适合做领导
Leadership looks good on you.
但看到你戴着访客胸牌却很别扭
Can't say the same for that visitor badge.
现如今可真是不太平
Ah, it's such a chaotic time.
你刚开始做局长
Your first as director,
所以我想来看看你干得如何
and I thought I should swing by and see how you were doing.
需要我提供什么建议吗
Any advice I can offer?
谢谢  我还应付得来
Thank you. I'm managing.
你呢
What about you?
毕竟要在外边对付暴动
I mean, out there in the streets with the riots.
是啊  大家很害怕
Yeah. People are scared, you know?
在部里也是如此
It's not much different in here.
我有个朋友  她可能有麻烦了
You know, a friend of mine, um, she might be in trouble,
菲奥纳·比姆  她在阿尔的酒吧工作
Fiona Byme, she works at Al's Bar.
你好啊  荣恩
Greetings, J'onn.
你好  布莱尼
Hey, Brainy.
我查看了第三大街到第八十六大街所有的街边摄像头
I checked all the cams along the boulevards from 3rd Street to 86th
-想要找到默茜  -然后呢
- for detection of Mercy. - And?
什么都没有找到
Nada. Not one lead.
看来你这里也挺忙的
You know what, um, looks like you got your hands full here,
我自己去找菲奥纳好了
I'll follow up with Fiona on my own.
我自己出去
I'll see myself out.
-好的  -保重
- Okay. - Take care.
我很想念他
I do miss him.
不是说我不喜欢你做领导
Not that I don't enjoy your leadership.
我能感觉到你对国家目前的状况感到气愤
I can sense that you're upset about the current state of the nation.
我想向你保证  根据我的计算
I'd like to assure you that based on my calculations,
此次暂时的危机不会对地球造成深刻影响
this moment of crisis does not deeply impact our planet.
不知你注意到没有  布莱尼
I don't know if you've noticed, Brainy,
我们现在并非身处未来
but we're not in the future.
而未来是可以改变的
And the future can change.
这是"损人"  你血糖低时就会损人
Ah, that was "snark." And you snark when your blood sugar is low.
我知道该如何帮助你
I know how to help you.
披萨
Pizza.
人类进食时似乎会平静下来
Humans seem to find calm in the consumption of food.
我根据计算得出结论  吃披萨
My calculations lead me to the conclusion that pizza
或许是此刻对所有人最有帮助的事情
might be the right thing at this very moment for everyone.
-快走  -好的
- Go. - All right.
这么快就过劳了吗
Working too hard already?
抱歉  咖啡
Sorry. Um, coffee.
咖啡  我需要喝些咖啡
Coffee. I need some coffee.
我去买些回来  你想要吗
I'm going to get some. Do you want some?
你想要  我去去就回
Yes, you do. I will be right back.
抱歉
Sorry.
朋友  今天吃什么  辣香肠还是菠萝
My friend, what's it going to be today, pepperoni, pineapple?
我要十二份大号披萨
I'll have a dozen large pizzas.
十一份什锦披萨  一份苹果橄榄披萨
Eleven with everything and one with apples and olives.
你先请
After you.
你们有浓缩咖啡吗
Um, do you make espressos?
我不知道你哥哥和默茜有这么多过往
I had no idea your brother's history with Mercy went back this far.
是啊
Yeah.
默茜最初是他的安全主管
Mercy started out as his head of security,
但时间久了  她成了他最亲密的知己
but over time she became his closest confidant
时常来吃晚饭
and frequent dinner guest.
我知道莱克斯过去和她关系很亲密
I knew Lex had a close relationship with her
可我不知道你也一样
but I had no idea you did.
你也知道  从小到大  我妈总爱挑我毛病
Growing up, my mother was very critical of me, as you know.
她很少帮我解决生活方面的问题
She wasn't very helpful with the life stuff.
然后默茜进入了我们的生活
Then Mercy came into our lives
可以说她对我很照顾
and she kind of took me under her wing.
她教我得体的举止和着装
She taught me how to act, how to dress,
以及如何达成最强有力的手段
how to always reach for the biggest gun.
她几乎像我姐姐一样  几乎
She was almost like a big sister. Almost.
她离开莱克斯后  你是不是也很难过
Was it hard for you after she left Lex?
是的  我觉得被抛弃了
Yeah. I felt abandoned.
但这不能怪她
But I really can't blame her.
说实话  我觉得全是莱克斯的错
Truthfully, I blame Lex entirely.
他们为什么分开
What happened between them?
默茜变得很沮丧
Mercy grew frustrated
因为莱克斯的心思全在超人身上
because Lex was so hyper-focused on Superman.
他不再从大局考虑
He lost sight of the bigger picture.
她觉得仅有智能是不够的
She felt intelligence wasn't enough,
人类需要开发
that humans needed to develop even
比外星人更强大的能力
greater powers and abilities than aliens.
-听着像疯话  -是啊
- That sounds unhinged. - Yeah.
但我不反对她的主要观点
But I don't disagree with her main point.
人类为什么不能像外星人一样强大
Well, why can't humans be as powerful as aliens?
这个...
Well--
出什么事了  伊芙
What is it, Eve?
-你知道凯文·奥吗  -当然知道
- You know Kevin Oh? - Of course I know him.
他是形象诱发器的主程序员
He's the chief programmer for our Image Inducers.
他死了  尸体是早上在公寓楼被发现的
He's dead. He was found at his apartment complex this morning.
我的天  太可怕了
Oh, my God, that's horrible.
他的笔记本电脑丢了  网络安全部刚刚来电话
His laptop was missing, and Cyber Security just called to say
说他的电脑被用来登陆主机了
that it's been used to log into the mainframe.
我必须在他们黑进来前拦截攻击
Well, then I have to block this hack before they can breach us.
进入L公司系统  请输入密码
密钥已认证
我该付你多少钱  朋友
How much do I owe you, my friend?
故障了  稍等
It's broke. One moment.
有人在系统里植入了特洛伊木马
Someone's put a trojan horse into the system.
病毒正试图破坏整个形象诱发器平台
It's trying to take down the entire Image Inducer platform.
第一位用户已经遭到袭击了
The first user has already been compromised.
布莱尼克五号
Brainiac-5?
假如我不能删除木马
If I don't delete the trojan,
全世界每位用户都会遭到暴露
then every user will be exposed. Worldwide.
-你是什么玩意  -你认识我
- What are you? - You know me.
我常来你这里买披萨
I purchased pizzas from you multiple times.
你是个叛徒  伙计们  这有个外星人
You're a traitor. Hey, guys, there's an alien out here.
肯定是默茜搞的鬼
This has to be Mercy's doing.
准是她没跑了
I'd bet considerable money on it.
暴力是人类最基本的情绪
Violence is the most basic human emotion
这应该是沟通失败后
and should only be a last resort
使用的最后一招
should communication fail.
该死  她入侵系统速度太快  我都来不及修补
Damn it! She's hacking the system faster than I can patch it.
你们要住手
You need to back off.
我说话结巴了吗  我说住手
Did I stutter? I said back off.
系统锁定完成
成功了
Got it.
连接中断
取消所有权限
我要封锁云端
Okay, I'm putting a lockdown on the cloud
这样就没人能通过电脑进入系统了
so no one can access the system through a computer.
默茜·格雷夫斯是绝对不可能黑进来的
Mercy Graves is never getting in here.
作为凯特科全球媒体公司的记者
As a reporter for CatCo Worldwide Media,
我一定会把我今天在这里目睹的暴力
I am going to make sure everyone knows about the violence
和残酷行为公诸于世
and cruelty I witnessed here today.
先生  你才是叛徒
You, sir, are the traitor.
快把他要的匹萨给他
Now, give him his pizzas.
我还以为他是我的朋友
I thought he was my friend.
真正的朋友会接受你的本来面目
A true friend will accept you for who you truly are.
你很眼熟
You look familiar.
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
应该不认识
I don't believe so.
我能不能
May I...
认识一下你
...get to know you?
应该可以
I think we can make that happen.
如何认识
Well, how?
我叫尼娅·纳尔
My name's Nia Nal.
如果你真的想找到我  你会找到我的
If you truly want to find me, you will.
菲奥纳&曼彻斯特婚礼
2019年3月31日
都有谁参与
涉及很多团体吗
好吧  菲奥纳
All right, Fiona,
我们试试11347
let's try 11347.
迪恩·佩特赛利
尼娅  一切还好吧
Nia, is everything okay?
我刚刚目睹了一位店家拒绝服务外星人
I just witnessed a business owner refuse to serve an alien
然后攻击了他
and then assault him.
嗯
Yeah.
最近我们接到很多这种电话
We're getting a lot of calls like that lately.
这种类型的报道值得我们去跟进
And it's good for us to follow up on these types of stories
这样人们就知道这些店家是如何对待外星人的
so that people know how these businesses are treating aliens.
当然  但是不止这样
Absolutely. But, it's bigger than that.
奥尔森先生  我认为
Mr. Olsen, I really think
我们需要主编的声明
we need a statement from our Editor-In-Chief.
外星人正在遭受前所未有的仇恨攻击
Aliens are being subjected to hate crimes like never before.
是很可怕
It is horrible.
所以我们要报道这些事件  没错
Which is why we are reporting on this kind of stuff. We are.
但是
But...
我必须从战略上来考虑
I have to think strategically.
我不适合在这个时候写社论
And this is not the best time for me to write an editorial.
我知道自从摘下守护者的面具
I know you've been under a lot of scrutiny
你接受着来自各方的审视
since unmasking as Guardian.
现在你又有机会为正义而战了
You have another chance to fight for justice now.
好
Okay.
请坐
Please.
你有什么想法
What's on your mind?
也许你不知道  我是变性人
You may not know this about me, but, I am a transgender woman.
我知道因为身份而遭人袭击
I know what it's like to be attacked and denied
和拒绝的滋味
because of who I am.
看到外星人遭到攻击时  我无法视而不见
When I saw that alien being attacked, I couldn't let it pass.
我
I...
我必须站出来
I had to stand up,
让恶霸看看自己的面目
hold a mirror to that bully's face.
我伸出了援手
And I made a difference.
但那只是针对一个人
And that was just one person.
你可是凯特科
You are the Editor-In-Chief
全球媒体公司的主编
of CatCo Worldwide Media,
你可以让整座城市直视其真面目
you can hold a mirror up to the entire city.
我们必须让人们看到
We have to show people
不可以用暴力对待外星人
that violence against aliens is not okay.
而我们生存下去的唯一方式
And that the only way we are going to survive
就是开始看到彼此的真实面目
is if we start truly seeing each other.
谢谢你分享自己的真心话
Thank you for sharing your truth
也谢谢你的热情
and your passion.
但有一点我也希望你能明白
But there's something else that I want you to understand, too,
与我们有同样价值观的读者
is that our readers that share our values
已经知道我们支持外星人了
already know that we support aliens.
那其他人呢
And what about the others?
我们在努力  逐渐扩大影响力
We're trying. We're reaching over the aisle.
如果我出声太早
If I editorialize too soon,
他们肯定会说我们有偏见
they're just going to call us biased.
他们会给我们贴上标签
They're going to prejudge us.
听我说  我已经干这行很久了
Look, I've been doing this for a long time
唯一能打动公众的就是客观报道
and the only way to reach people is through balanced reporting.
无辜的人们遭受了攻击  重要的不是客观
When innocent people are being attacked, it's not about balance.
而是公正
It's about justice.
话说  这些披萨要叫大家一起吃吗
So, are you going to let the staff in on all these pizzas
还是我们俩把它们全部拿下
or, are you and I just going to knock them out ourselves?
我愿意接受这项挑战
Because challenge accepted.
好啊  请自便
Yes, please help yourself.
这是苹果橄榄的  我的最爱
This is apples and olives. It's my favorite.
卡拉给我打了个电话
So, Kara just called me and, uh,
她说你的形象诱发器被入侵了
she said your Image Inducer was hacked?
对  很短暂的一会
Yes. It was just for a moment.
我一直在查那次小故障的源头
I've been trying to find the source of the glitch
命令似乎来自于
and it seems it was a command
L公司一位高级程序员的电脑
from the computer of a senior L-Corp programmer.
她和莉娜觉得是默茜干的
Well, she and Lena think that Mercy's responsible.
莉娜已经开启了防火墙  没人能入侵系统了
So Lena put up a firewall, no one can hack into the system.
也就是说  默茜要想操控形象诱发器
That means the only way Mercy can access the Image Inducer now
只能去L公司的主机
is through the mainframe at L-Corp,
我刚对她的行为进行了模拟
and based on the simulation I just created for her,
她有99.99%的可能性已经在路上了
there is a 99.99% chance that she is on her way there now.
什么声音
What's that?
-整个建筑都封锁了  -默茜来了
- The building's in lockdown. - Mercy's here.
-我们不能留在这里  -是啊  等等
- We can't stay here. - I know. But wait.
我不建议你这么保护自己  戴上
These aren't my security alarms. Put these in.
你感觉到了吗  是声波攻击
Did you feel that? It's a sonic attack.
默茜已经除掉了整个安保团队
Mercy's taken out our whole security team
控制了整栋建筑  怎么做到的呢
and got control of the whole building. But how?
默茜曾是莱克斯安保团队的负责人
When Mercy was head of Lex's security,
整个系统都是她设计的
she designed the whole system.
卡拉  等等  你不能进去  我们封锁了
Kara, wait. No, no, you can't go out there. We're on lockdown.
任何人不许进出
There's no going in or out.
我应该在哪里躲着吗  有没有
Well, should I hide somewhere, is there,
什么衣柜之类可以藏人的地方
like, a closet, or somewhere I can lay low?
现在对你来说最安全的地方就是跟我在一起
The safest place for you to be right now is with me.
-默茜很危险  但我知道如何对付她  -好
- I know Mercy's dangerous, but I know how to handle her. - Okay.
默茜想关掉主机
Mercy's trying to shut down the mainframe.
但因为我安装了防火墙
But since I installed the firewall,
她唯一的办法就是手动操作
the only way for her to do that is a manual override.
我们只用防止她碰到服务器
All we have to do is stop her from getting to the servers.
非常不错
Well, well, well,
你的策略很好
I love the ren-o, Lena.
不过  我很惊讶
Although, I'm a little surprised
你居然让整个建筑都联网了
you've put the whole building online.
不像你风格
So unlike you.
她可真"有趣"
Well, she's fun.
计划如何  要分头行动吗
Okay, so, what's the plan? Do we split up?
当然不要  人多力量大
Absolutely not. Safety in numbers.
小心
Watch out.
-卡拉  你还好吗  -我没事
- Kara, are you okay? - Yeah.
默茜请的狙击手技术不行
Mercy must have hired terrible marksmen.
完全没打到我
They totally missed me.
我一直想知道莉娜的公司会是什么样
I always wondered what the house of Lena would look like.
比我想象中的更有创意
But this is more innovative and imaginative
-更有想象力  -你低估我了
- than even I expected. - You underestimated me.
-这是侮辱  -你很有天分
- It's insulting. - You have a gift
我不想浪费
and I don't intend to squander it.
她那话到底是什么意思
What did she mean by that?
-系统出问题了吗  -我不知道
- Glitch in the system? - I don't know.
超女  超女  你在吗
Supergirl? Supergirl, are you there?
坚持住
Just hang on.
艾丽克斯  是我  卡拉
Alex, hi, hi. It's, uh, yeah, it's Kara.
我和莉娜还有伊芙在一起
I'm here with Lena and Eve.
你还没能甩开她们吗
So you haven't been able to get away?
对  没错
Uh, yup. Yeah, that's right.
超女还没到现场
Supergirl has not arrived on the scene.
-超查部要来了吗  -四分钟后我给你一支队伍
- Is the DEO coming? - I can have a team to you in four minutes.
三分二十六秒
Three minutes 26 seconds.
-你看到默茜了吗  -每台监控器上都有
- Have you seen Mercy yet? - Only on every monitor in the place.
你在哪里
Where are you now?
莉娜  这是哪里
Lena, where are we?
东楼  三层  B走廊
East Wing, third floor, corridor B.
-布莱尼给你找地方换衣服  -好的
- Brainy's going to find a place for you to change. - Great.
西侧八米左右有一间杂物间
There's a broom closet 27 feet to the west.
等等  不行
Uh, wait, no.
默茜的雇佣兵有78%的可能
There's a 78% chance that Mercy's mercenaries
会从那个方向过来
will approach from that direction.
行  那我们还能往哪去
Okay, any other options?
有个没人的原型实验室  在你身后40英尺
A proto-lab, unoccupied. 40 feet behind you.
-等等  -怎么  默茜在那边吗
- Wait. - What is it? Is Mercy there?
对  对
Yes, yes.
又不对  不对
Rather no, no.
她有76.8%的可能会通过那条走廊
There's a 76.8% chance that she'll be using that corridor
到达服务器机房  呃不  是67%
to reach the server room. Uh, 67%.
布莱尼  到底是哪边
Brainy, which is it?
是
The...
没时间了  走  快走
We don't have time. Go. Go!
不好意思  我今天忘记吃抗敏药了
I'm sorry, I forgot to take my allergy medicine today.
我们得离开这里  快走
We need to get out of here, come on.
伊芙  别弄了  快走
Eve, enough. Come on.
等等
Wait, wait.
这些门上有隐藏的快速关门阀
These doors were built with a hidden quick-release.
我高中有个暑假在主题公园工作过
I spent a summer in high school working at a theme park.
我是兔女郎
I was a bunny.
-厉害  -这样啊  好
- Cool. - Okay, right.
伊芙  你去控制室
Eve, you get to the control room
看看能不能解除默茜对大楼的控制
and see if you can wrestle this building away from Mercy.
我们去服务器那里  行吗
We'll get to the servers, okay?
我觉得我在这更安全  这门看着够结实...
I really think I'm safer here. This door looks so strong--
好  卡拉  我保证
Okay, all right, Kara, I promise you,
你跟我一起更安全  好吧  我保护你
you are safer with me, all right? I got you.
-行吗  伊芙  去吧  -好
- Okay? Eve, come on. - Right.
她当然会来这里了
Of course she would come here.
这是哪里  什么东西
Where is here? What is this?
这是我存放所有实验原型的地方
It's where I keep all my experimental prototypes.
别把这报道出去
Don't print that.
拿我记者的身份保证
Reporter's honor.
你妈妈的莱克斯奥服
Your mother's Lexosuit.
对  散架了
Yeah, it's in pieces.
这里不应该还有只手臂吗
Shouldn't there be another arm here?
默茜拿了更大的那把枪
Mercy took the bigger gun.
我必须把它给交给你
I have to hand it to you.
这战服是死亡的完美利器
This suit is such an exquisite instrument of death.
这种发明能推动人类进入
This creation could really move humans into a new phase
完美体能的新纪元
of physical excellence.
我知道  所以我才造它出来
I know. That's why I made it.
那加入我吧
Well, then, join me.
一旦我们毁灭了形象诱发器
Once we destroy the Image Inducers,
外星人就无法再隐藏在暗处
then the aliens are going to go crawling into the light
我们就知道在和谁斗争
and then we'll know exactly who we're fighting.
我不想和他们斗争  默茜
I don't want to fight them, Mercy.
这不是L公司的宗旨吗
Isn't that what L-Corp is all about?
为了掌权和优越感而斗争
Your fight for control and superiority?
不  宗旨是为世界做贡献
No, it's about doing good for the world
证明卢瑟家的清白
and helping clear the Luthor name.
你还记得以前
Do you remember when you were afraid
你害怕给莱克斯看你的小发明吗
to show Lex your little inventions?
你会把它们藏起来  不让他发现
That you would hide them from him
不天衣无缝不给他看
until they were absolutely perfect?
你还记得他会怎么做吗
Do you remember what he would do?
记得
Yeah.
他会说它们很可爱  我应该把它们做成粉色的
He'd say they were cute and I should make them in pink.
这正是他所害怕的
This is exactly what he was afraid of.
他怕你会比他更优秀
That you would outshine him.
我知道你想抵抗
I know that you want to resist.
但你跟我一样
But you are just like me.
你不必成为最优秀的
You don't want to just be the best,
你就是最优秀的
you are the best.
我知道我是最优秀的
Oh, I know I'm the best.
而你才是那个没充分发挥自己潜力的人
You're the one not living up to your full potential.
你选择了支持其中一方
You've chosen a side.
而我不会这么做
I'd never do that.
你只在乎怎么敛财
All you care about is lining your pockets.
是啊  而且她也不是杀人凶手  所以...
Yeah. Also, she's not a murderer, so...
那可能只是因为她还没有试过
Maybe that's just because she hasn't tried it yet.
-你射偏了  -我根本没有瞄准
- You missed. - I wasn't really aiming.
别  等下
No, wait.
你不知道它升级了吧
Guess you didn't see the upgrade,
现在是左臂上武器更多
'cause the left arm's got more goods now.
-卡拉  出去  -好
- Kara, get out. - Uh, okay.
你配不上卢瑟这个名字
You don't deserve the Luthor name,
地球的叛徒
Earth traitor.
你话说反了
You got that backwards.
卢瑟这个名字配不上莉娜
The Luthor name doesn't deserve Lena.
超女
Supergirl.
我想问你怎么绕过封锁的  但是
I'd ask how you bypassed a lockdown but--
但是你处在危机中所以很高兴见到我
But you're in a crisis and you're happy to see me?
是的  谢谢你
Yes. Thank you.
他们说格雷夫斯姐弟在被悬赏缉拿
You know what, they say the Graves twins are collector's items.
复古莱克斯时代
Vintage Lex Era.
我听说他们会升值
Well, I hear that they're worth more.
如果他们一直被关在牢房里
If they never come out of the box.
人们很愤怒
The people are angry,
丹弗斯特工
Agent Danvers.
他们的恐惧正在蔓延
Their fear is metastasizing.
你无法阻止
And you can't stop it.
你没错  我不能
You're right. I can't.
改变心灵和思想  我不擅长这些
Changing hearts and minds, that's not really my thing.
我擅长这些
It's mine.
她很擅长这个
And she's really good at it.
有人觉得这很好笑吗
Somebody thinks this is funny?
这不好笑  我只是想工作而已
This isn't funny. I'm just trying to work here.
谁干的
Who did it?
谁把木屑放进我的咖啡杯里的
Who put wood chips in my coffee cup?
我以为树人吃木屑呢
I thought that's what Dryads ate.
木头和石头
Wood and stone?
我私下告诉你的
I told you that in confidence.
怎么回事  麦肯齐
Hey. What's going on here, Mackenzie?
只是个无聊的恶作剧
It was just a dumb prank.
在这里我们尊重别人
We respect people here.
对不起  弗兰克林
I'm sorry, Franklin.
你们知道吗  大伙儿
You know what, guys?
迁就我一下  我知道很晚了
Just humor me for a second. I know it's late.
我知道你们有些人对于总统的所作所为很失望
Look, I know some of you are upset about what the president did,
但是那并不改变
but that does not change
我们作为一个国家或是出版社的身份
who we are as a country or as a publication.
凯特科不能容忍
CatCo does not tolerate hate
公司内部或是我们报纸上的仇视
within these walls or on our pages.
我们作为记者的职责就是揭露真相
And it is our duty as journalists to expose the truth.
无知是我们的敌人
And ignorance is our enemy,
相互之间不是
not each other.
谢谢你
Thank you.
记住这个
Remember that.
感觉很奇怪  不是吗  詹森
Feels strange, doesn't it, Jensen?
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
我打赌当你加入这个组织时
I bet when you joined this organization,
你从没想过你会
you never thought you'd
把人类关进牢笼里  是吗
be throwing humans in these cages, did you?
我的工作就是维持人类和外星人间的和平
My job is to maintain peace amongst humans and aliens alike.
他们袭击我们
They attack us,
欺骗我们
deceive us,
那些脏东西想要变成我们  詹森特工
those roaches want to be us, Agent Jensen.
所以他们才会来到这里
And that's why they're here.
他们为了我们的星球而来
They came for our planet.
而你的工作是保护我们的星球
And your job is to protect that.
但是你却在这里  与地球叛变者
And yet here you are, working side by side
与外星人同事
with Earth traitors and aliens.
不  我相信丹弗斯局长
No, I trust Director Danvers.
我发过誓言
And I took an oath.
总统也发过誓
So did the president.
好像没人可以信任了  对吧
It's like there's no one left to trust, right?
我是说  连总统都撒谎  我们还能信谁
I mean, if the president lies, who can we believe in?
这个国家正在分崩离析
This country is falling apart.
对不起  抱歉打扰了  但那真是太对了
Excuse me. Um, sorry to interrupt. But that is so true.
是吧  现在不像我们当时长大一样  对吧
Yeah, right? It's not like when we were growing up, right?
是啊  世界的确变了很多
Yeah. Yeah, I mean, the world sure has changed a lot.
我就是跟不上
I just can't keep up.
我在街上当巡警
I work the streets as a beat cop
我觉得随着时间流逝
and I just feel older
我年纪大了  更不懂这个世界了
and less relevant with every passing day.
什么社区
Uh, what neighborhood?
-肖尔伍德  -我有个朋友住在那附近
- Shorewood. - You know, I have a friend from around there.
在社区里做很多事情
Um, does a lot of work in the community,
比姆  菲奥纳·比姆  你认识她吗
um, Byme, Fiona Byme, do you know her?
不  我会记得那个名字
No, I'd remember that name.
这世上叫菲奥纳的并不多  也许有天会认识
Well, not a lot of Fionas in the world, so maybe someday.
-对  没错  -我走了
- Right. Yeah. - I'm off.
-保重  -很高兴和你谈话
- Take care. - Good talking to you.
答案是清洁间  我就知道
The answer was the broom closet. I knew it.
即使是一级智力
Even a first-level intellect
也会知道是清洁间
would know that it was the broom closet.
我为什么没和超女说
Why didn't I tell Supergirl that?
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
我告诉了超女错误的路线
I told Supergirl to go the wrong way.
她本可能会被抓
She could have gotten caught.
人无完人  布莱尼
Everyone makes mistakes, Brainy.
不  我是完人
No. No, not me.
我预测事件
I predict eventualities with
有着98.525%的准确率
a 98.525% accuracy rating.
在这次之前能达到99.12%呢
It used to be 99.12% before this happened.
这次是指今天在披萨店发生的事吗
Is this about what happened at the pizza place today?
我的形象诱发器失灵时
When my Image Inducer malfunctioned,
我发现了马西莫相当令人讨厌的一点
I discovered something rather unsavory about Massimo.
他好像不喜欢我本来的模样
It appears he didn't appreciate my natural visage.
他那时不知道你是外星人
He didn't know you were an alien.
他不只是惊讶而已  而是...
He wasn't just surprised, he was...
很生气
He was angry.
我知道人们害怕他们不认识的东西
I know that people fear what they do not know
但是马西莫认识我啊
but Massimo knew me.
而且虽然我来自天鸽座
And being from Colu does not change the fact
但我还是那个巴尼
that I am also Barney
喜欢橄榄苹果披萨的巴尼啊
of the olives and apples pizza.
巴尼
Barney?
巴尼是我在那家店买东西的化名
Barney is my pizza and coffee name.
看着我
Look at me.
不是每个人都像马西莫一样
Not everyone is like Massimo.
我知道在人类与外星同胞的磨合期
I knew that Earth would face a short period of unrest
地球会面临一小阵动乱
while humans adjusted to their alien compatriots,
-我从来没想到  -伤害了这么多人
- I just never expected it to - To hurt so much?
对不起
Sorry.
但下一次有人要伤害你的时候
But the next time someone tries to hurt you,
你把他们送到我这来
you send them my way.
你是个真正的朋友
You're a true friend.
所有外星人都值得拥有一个艾丽克斯·丹弗斯
All aliens deserve an Alex Danvers.
好吧
Well...
詹森  你有什么想和我说的吗
Jensen. Hey, is there something you want to say to me?
没有  女士  一切都好
No, ma'am. Everything's copacetic.
很好  每小时向我汇报一次
Good. I'd like an update every hour.
好的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
美国的同胞们
Fellow citizens of America,
现在局势复杂
these are complicated times.
你们之中有些人困惑  很多人害怕
Some of you are confused, many of you are scared.
你们刚刚发现  美国总统
You just found out that the President of the United States
并不像你们所想的那样来自北爱荷华
is not from Northern Iowa, like you thought.
她来自地球外广阔宇宙中的某个星球
She's from a planet somewhere out in the vast universe.
你们很多人因为总统撒谎而感觉被背叛了
Many of you feel betrayed because you were lied to.
马斯丁总统也承担了后果
President Marsdin took responsibility for that.
她辞职了
She resigned from office.
但这个国家的恐惧如星火燎原般扩散
But the fear that's spreading in this country like wildfire
并不是因为总统撒了谎
isn't because the president lied.
正义为贵
而是因为她来自不同的地方
It's because she comes from some place different.
你们都知道我也来自一个不同的地方
All of you know that I am also from a different place,
另一个星球
another planet.
但是我在这里生活了很久
But I've lived here long enough to know
久到已经明白出生地并不要紧
that it doesn't matter where we were born
因为我们都是一样的
because we are all the same.
超女全国演说
地球人人或外星人的角色
The character of a person or alien
并非由出生地定义的
is not defined by where we are from,
而是由行为定义的
but by what we do.
爆料马斯丁总统的人想要分裂我们
The people that exposed President Marsdin wanted to divide us.
他们想让我们攻击彼此
They want us to turn on one another,
生于恐惧  长于怨恨
live in fear, grow in hate.
但是我知道我们不会沦落至此
But I know we are better than that.
我知道我们可以怀着爱与尊重团结在一起
I know we can work together with love and respect,
用善良对待我们的邻居
treat our neighbors with kindness.
我是外星人  我爱这个我傲以为家的星球
I'm an alien and I love this planet that I am proud to call home.
我们心愿一致  当一个好的美国人
I want what we all want, to be a good American.
我会支持新政府
I will stand by the new administration
因为这个国家开始恢复正常了
as this nation begins to heal.
我会继续像往常一样
And I'll continue to protect
保护我的朋友们和邻居们
my friends and neighbors just as I always have.
我希望你们都能这样做
I hope you will all do the same.
你觉得蓝色是正确的决定吗
You think blue's the right decision?
我想戴红色的  但他们都告诉我
I wanted to go with red but they all told me
蓝色在电视上更彰显总统气派
that blue was more presidential on TV.
我觉得你很有总统气派  先生  你会很棒的
I think you look very presidential, sir. You're gonna be great.
这一切都发生得太快了
This all happened so quickly.
但我想感谢你抓住了默茜·格雷夫斯
But I want to thank you for capturing Mercy Graves.
我们还在积极追捕她的同伙
Well, we are still actively pursuing any of her associates.
我知道恐惧在发酵  但我们会克服的
I know fear is growing but we will overcome this.
我还担心你可能不会支持我
I, uh, I was worried you might not be behind me.
我知道你忠于总统  忠于奥利维亚
I know you are loyal to the president, to Olivia.
我忠于这个国家  阁下
I am loyal to this country, sir.
无论总统是谁
No matter who runs it.
能得到你的帮助  我很荣幸  倍受鼓舞
Well, I am honored and encouraged to have your help.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不用谢
Of course.
贝克总统  我
Uh, President Baker? Can I...
好了
There you go.
-你能行的  阁下  -谢谢你
- You got this, sir. - Thank you.
我接受美国总统
I accept the responsibility of the office
职位的任职
of the President of the United States.
-我庄严宣誓  -詹森  我问一下
- I do solemnly swear... - Jensen, hey, I'm just checking in
默茜和奥蒂斯的最新情况
for an update of Mercy and Otis.
詹森特工  你在吗
Agent Jensen, are you there?
始终保护和守卫
...preserve to protect and defend...
调出那个牢房监控
Um, pull up the camera on that containment cell.
奥蒂斯看起来很焦虑
Otis seems anxious.
他都这样走来走去一个多小时了
He's been pacing around that cell for the past hour.
等一下
Wait a minute.
看那
Look at that.
那有一个停顿
That's a stutter step.
他没被绊到  那是个小故障
He's not tripping, that's a glitch.
安保摄像信息被破坏了
The security feed's been breached.
那只是一个全息图
It's a hologram.
人挺多的  对吗
This is some crowd, isn't it?
有多少人昨天失业
How many of you lost your jobs yesterday?
我失业了
I did.
我知道有很多人
I know it's a lot of hands.
我很抱歉  老实说
I'm so sorry. And if I'm being honest,
我与你们同在
I'm right there with you.
让我再问你们一个问题
Let me ask you another question.
有多少人因为外星人攻击而失去了家园
How many of you have lost your home to an alien attack?
有多少人的孩子还在做噩梦
How many of your children still have nightmares?
你们中有多少人去找过工作
How many of you have gone looking for a job?
一份你急需的工作
A job that you desperately need.
但你又没能得到它  为什么
But you don't get that job. Why?
因为你没有超能力
Because you don't have super strength.
法律要求"不歧视"
The law says, "No discrimination."
但是  当然  总说
But, of course, it's always
"保护外星人  保卫外星人"
"Protect the aliens, protect the aliens."
谁来保护我们
Who's going to protect us?
肯定不会是政府
Surely not the government.
谁会允许一个外星人
Who allowed an alien to
来当美国的总统
become the President of the United States?
-你不害怕吗  -害怕
- Doesn't that scare you? - Yeah.
这会吓到你  真奇怪
That's weird that it should scare you
因为超女说要心怀希望
because Supergirl says that you should have hope.
站着说话不腰疼   她是个外星人
It's easy for her to say, she's an alien.
你们知道我想让你们感受到什么吗
Do you know what I want you to feel?
我想你们感到恐惧
I want you to feel fear.
-这可能会激励你  -是的
- It might energize you. - Yeah.
因为当这个国家的最高职位
Because when the highest office of this country
被一个外星人所占据
can be infiltrated and occupied by an alien,
-没有人是安全的  -没人安全
- none of us are safe. - No.
她们都有超能力
All of them have super powers.
外星人一旦发起进攻
Which one of you alone is strong enough to protect yourself
你们谁有能力一个人保护自己
should that alien decide to attack, and they will!
是的
Yeah!
所以我们要做什么
So what do we do?
我们要团结一心
Because we can come together
我们可以消灭这个
and we can tear out this alien
威胁着我们世界的外星毒瘤
disease that threatens to poison our world,
我们可以要求他们从哪来回哪去
we can invite them to return to the planets that they came from
我们的国家就可以
and we can restore health
恢复健康  重现活力  再度安全
and vitality and security to this country.
而我  作为你们自由的代表
And I, as your Agent of Liberty,
我与你们同在
will stand with you
因为我们敢把地球放在第一位
as we dare to put Earth first!
让我听见你们的呼声
Let me hear you say it.
地球第一  地球第一  地球第一
Earth first! Earth first! Earth first!